[
  {
    "question": "Does Braden have Airpods?",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Ayush eat meat",
    "answer" : false
  },
  {
    "question": "Evan isn't as Canadian as he thinks he is",
    "answer" : true
  },
  {
    "question": "Sage Pierone is Wakandan",
    "answer" : false
  },
  {
    "question": "They call Ian McThick",
    "answer" : true
  },
  {
    "question": "Michael is a D1 rapper",
    "answer" : true
  },
  {
    "question": "Digimon is better than Pokemon",
    "answer" : false
  },
  {
    "question": "the antiderivative of e^x is e^x",
    "answer" : true
  },
  {
    "question": "Manav is vegetarian",
    "answer" : false
  },
  {
    "question": "Charles is a SAT GOD",
    "answer" : true
  }

]